(Leonard:)No. She cannot kiss...
What is wrong with you people?!
(Penny:)- Leonard...
- No, no, no. It's not okay.
(Awkward guy:)Who are you?
(Leonard:)I'm her husband.
(Awkward guy:)No, you're not.
(Leonard:)I am.
(Penny:)Yeah, he really is.
(Penny:)No.
(Howard:)It's got a rearview camera,
there's a DVD player--
(Howard:)oh, and check this out.
(Howard:)It's like we're living
in the future!
Hey, show her the trunk!
Show her the trunk!
Imagine this:
you've got the baby in one hand,
(Howard:)groceries in the other,
and you're thinking,
"How am I gonna
open this trunk?"
(Bernadette:)I'm probably thinking,
"Where's my husband,
and why isn't he helping me?"
(Howard:)You don't need my help
when you can open the trunk
(Howard:)with a simple kick of the foot.